{
    "id": "98a617880f124bf7a5bbcdfadf82a4a5",
    "title": "Present Perfect Continuous Tenses Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "How long ...................................... for?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "are you waiting",
                "have you been waiting",
                "have you waited"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "fdd33df5ff614cf094377cf8c148a5db"
        },
        {
            "question": "We ........................................ in this street for twenty years.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "are living",
                "have been living",
                "live"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "5c0e2da430d5486aa9e406f2f8effb7c"
        },
        {
            "question": "He ........................................... in the garden since morning.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is working",
                "has been working",
                "work"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "a2d6e4f012a24e5882c82468e2924cd3"
        },
        {
            "question": "It ....................................... since yesterday.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is raining",
                "rained",
                "has been raining"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "18570428f1a54259a4529aa43947b633"
        },
        {
            "question": "I .................................................... this laptop for three years.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "am using",
                "use",
                "have been using"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "b58353df40e8450385525dff46ae696d"
        },
        {
            "question": "The workers ......................................... higher wages for a long time.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "has been demanding",
                "have been demanding",
                "demand"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "46bc6db5b2e44b3fadf6d89bbb982d66"
        },
        {
            "question": "The girl .......................................... her lessons.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "has been learning",
                "have been learning",
                "had been learning"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "6c7d29dd42b54251b2ea597356533280"
        },
        {
            "question": "The children ................................................. in the garden.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "has been playing",
                "have been playing",
                "had been playing"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "76b7ec6a38b7481c8b77c3e491d6652b"
        },
        {
            "question": "‘You look tired.’ ‘Yes, I ............................................’",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "am running",
                "have been running",
                "has been running"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "647ff646cb5a4ac6b4464ed776025d72"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who .............................................. in my bed?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is sleeping",
                "has been sleeping",
                "have been sleeping"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "e57aec4054784b2580e3172fc9ad049b"
        }
    ]
}